var questions = [{
  
    "question": "What is Pending intent in android?",
    "choices": ["kind of intent","use to pass data between activity","fire at future point of time","None of above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }, {
    "question": "What is android view group?",
    "choices": ["collection of views","base class of bulding block","Layouts","None of above"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "What is sleep mode in android?",
    "choices": ["radio interface layer","switched off","Airplane Mode","None of Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "Which permissions are require to get a location in android?",
    "choices": ["ACCESS_FINE & ACCESS_COARSE","GPRS","INTERNET","WIFI"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "What are debugging techniques available in android?",
   "choices": ["DDMS","Breaking Point","Memory Profile","All of Above"],
   " correctAnswer": 3
  }, {
    "question": "How to fix crash using logcat in android?",
    "choices": ["Gmail","Google search","Name along with line number","None of above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }, {
    "question": "How to find JSON element length in android?",
    "choices": ["count()","sum()","add()","length()"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  }, {
    "question": "Which is magic constant of PHP return class method name?",
    "choices": ["_METHOD_","_FILE_","_FUNCTION_","_CLASS_"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "Which function is use to read file content?",
    "choices": ["fopen()","fread()","filesize()","file_exist()"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }, {
    "question": "Which function is use to get cookies in PHP?",
    "choices": ["getcookie()","$_COOKIE","isset()","None of Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },{
    "question": "Which is used to parse an XML document in PHP?",
    "choices": ["simplexml_load_string()","loadxml()","Both A and B","None of above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }, {
    "question": "What is size of short variable?",
    "choices": [8,16,32,64],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }, {
    "question": "What is default value of int?",
    "choices": [0,"0.0","null","Not of Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "What is default value of local variable?",
    "choices": ["null",0,"depend on variable","not assign"],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  }, {
    "question": "Method overloading is example of?",
    "choices": ["static binding","dnamic binding","Both","None of Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "Can you assign anonymous function to a variable?",
    "choices": ["true","false"],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  }, {
    "question": "Which of following JQuery method remove set of method element?",
    "choices": ["empty()","delete()","remove(expr)","none of above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }, {
    "question": "Which is JQuery method sets the height property of element?",
    "choices": ["set height()","set height(value)","height(value)","None of Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  }, {
    "question": "Which return the character at specific index?",
    "choices": ["characterAt()","charAt()","getcharAt()","None of Above"],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
   {
    "question": "Which method reverse the order in an array?",
     "choices":["changeorder()","reverse()","sort(order)","None of Above"],
   "correctAnswer": 1
  }];
  
 